http://www.pwcenter.org/privacy-policy

Our Supporters
Become a memberExclusive access to our playwriting opportunities database, advice from experts, and chances to connect with other writers.
Search
Become a memberExclusive access to our playwriting opportunities database, advice from experts, and chances to connect with other writers.
learn moresign up todayalready have an account?
Search
Become a memberExclusive access to our playwriting opportunities database, advice from experts, and chances to connect with other writers.
learn moresign up todayalready have an account?
Revised May 24, 2018
The Playwrights’ Center (“Center”) understands your concerns about information privacy and is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We will not collect any personally identifiable information during your visit to this website unless you voluntarily submit this information.
Use of information that you provide
The Center may use your personally identifiable information (name, address, telephone, email, etc.) gathered from membership, class registrations, donations, and event registration, to provide you with information from the Center. The Center will never share your information with other organizations and will not provide your name to any other organization for the purposes of soliciting you for a financial contribution. We will not voluntarily provide your personal information to any institution that wishes to sell its products to you or to harass you with “junk mail.”
If you wish you may opt out of these exchanges by one of the methods listed below under “Request for removal.”
Playwrights’ Center members: The required information to set up a Playwrights’ Center membership is name, email address, ZIP code, and country. All other information in voluntary. Members who set up profiles on our website can choose their profile privacy setting: private, only visible to other members, or public.
Financial information
The Center will protect any personal financial information that you share with us. Our secure server encrypts all personal information so that it cannot be read as it is transmitted over the internet. If you make a purchase on this site, we will use your credit card number only to process your payment and will not use it for marketing purposes. We will keep order information in our records for a limited period of time, but this information is never shared with third parties nor is it stored in our database.
Disclosure
The Center website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Center or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the Center; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Center, or the public.
Voluntary participation and severance
By using the Center website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. You may request that the Center no longer use your personally identifiable information by one of the methods listed below. The Center will remove your information at the earliest opportunity after receiving your request.
Disclaimer
Although the Center will make every effort to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures and usage of personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The Center currently uses cookies to store constituents’ preferences and record session information such as items that consumers add while signing up for membership or registering for classes. Cookies are also used to record page location to assist with navigation and menus on our site.
Security
The Center currently uses Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to encrypt sensitive information, such as financial information, while that data travels over the Internet.
Warning about fraudulent emails
“Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other highly personal information through email.
Links
Our site includes links to other websites. The Center is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites other than pwcenter.org.
Request for removal/change of information
You have the right to request that your personal data be corrected, provided to you, or removed from our website and database. If you wish to have your personally identifiable information removed from or changed, please notify us by one of the following methods:
Send an email to info@pwcenter.org.
Call us or leave a message at 612-332-7481
Send your request in writing to: Playwrights’ Center, 2301 East Franklin Avenue, Minneapolis, MN 55406
Whichever method you choose, include the name, address, and/or email address that you wish to have removed. For changes of information, please include both your old and new contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections.
Your consent
By using our website, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this online privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy so we encourage you to review it periodically.
Social
